Eric Shumway

1777 W 4650 S Apt. D, Roy Ut, 84067 (803)719-6925

eric shumway@yahoo.com linkedin.com/in/eric-shumway-493009228 https://github.com/eshumway1045

Summary

I currently have 5 years experience in Retail and customer satisfaction. I am passionate about coding and the things that it can bring to live. I have really come to love seeing the way code can change and shape websites, and the user experience. I continue to love learning how coding is continually changing and the ways that what another coder accomplish makes all of our lives easier, as well as looking for ways to be the one who changes how things are done.

Skills

- JavaScript
- MySQL
- HTML
- SQL
- Git
- MongoDB

<u>Projects</u>

- Budgetek https://github.com/eshumway1045/Budgetek
- Simple day planner https://eshumway1045.github.io/simple-planner/

Experience

- 09/08/2019 to 02/01/2021
 - Product Flow Specialist, Best Buy
- 02/01/2021 to 05/09/2021
 - Product Flow Supervisor, Best Buy
- 05/09/2021 to current
 - Product Flow Specialist, Best Buy

Education and Training

- Full Stack development bootcamp
- Bachelors in Computer Science at Weberstate University.
 - Currently in progress